export const salesforce1WeOffer = [
  {
    question: "Salesforce Consulting",
    answer:
      "Our dedicated professional CRM experts can help you advance your sales cloud, pardot, marketing cloud capabilities, realizing the full potential of your Salesforce implementation.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Customization",
    answer:
      "We will provide you with many exceptional salesforce customization solutions with the best salesforce development services from dashboard customization to layout and logic.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Integration",
    answer:
      "Integrate Salesforce with any cloud or on-premises system like ERP, Marketing Automation Platforms, and Order Management Systems to get your business experience 360-degree operational visibility.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Implementation",
    answer:
      "Get result-oriented Salesforce CRM implementation services to implement a wide range of Salesforce solutions from different industry verticals, to eliminate all complexities and bottlenecks.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Support",
    answer:
      "Get the right level of support from performance monitoring, maintenance, and feature enhancement to ensure stable performance and quick enhancement when needed.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce App Development",
    answer:
      "Leverage or end to end Salesforce app development services to build intelligent Salesforce solutions. We have top-of-the-line expertise in remodeling your business beyond the standard functionalities.",
  },
  {
    question: "Force.com Development",
    answer:
      "Streamline your business workflow and fulfill the functional business needs by developing custom applications on Force.com aligned to tailored versions of your Salesforce solution.",
  },
];
export const salesforce2WeOffer = salesforce1WeOffer;
export const salesforce3WeOffer = [
  {
    question: "24/7 Salesforce CRM Support",
    answer:
      "Get 24/7 salesforce CRM support and maintenance services to make sure your Salesforce solutionâ€™s performance is always above the mark. Our experts will find a solution for you regardless of how the complex the issue may be.",
  },
  {
    question: "Instant administration support",
    answer:
      "We support your Salesforce solution on a daily basis. You can send any requests to our administrators and they will implement your tasks instantly in a sandbox, such as custom reports or workflows, then our QA checks the implementation in the sandbox and deploys changes to the production environment.",
  },
  {
    question: "Bug Fixing",
    answer:
      "Our professional Salesforce consultants and developers help you keep up and running your existing system by mitigating bugs from the current infrastructure. All performance-centric issues will be solved with the utmost care & precision.",
  },
  {
    question: "Help desk for users",
    answer:
      "We provide 24/7/365 support for our clients. Users can use the JIRA service desk to contact our support team.",
  },
  {
    question: "Data administration & security",
    answer:
      "We clean, maintain, back up, and import your data on a daily basis with deduplication and validation rules. We also set up additional security measures to protect your data.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Maintenance",
    answer:
      "We will resolve all issues with our comprehensive range of Salesforce maintenance services. We use user management, security management, reporting, and routine checkups are a few best services that keep your CRM solution smooth and functional.",
  },
  {
    question: "Integration Updates and Support",
    answer:
      "Gone are the days you will have to wait for updates, now have real time synchronization at your fingertips. We will monitor your integrations, troubleshoot any updates and issues and finally, help you build custom API integrations to keep you at the top.",
  },
  {
    question: "Regular Administration",
    answer:
      "Our work keeps on even after successful Salesforce integration and implementation services. We keep an eye on your solution and offer you support services like security management, making the solution bugs-free, demo and etc.",
  },
];

export const salesforce4WeOffer = [
  {
    question: "Advisory & consultancy",
    answer:
      "Adopting a new CRM is a complicated and risky task; our certified Salesforce Consultant is always available for strategic advice to start with the right approach and on the right foot. We help you review the system, understand business challenges, create a roadmap, and opt for the right Salesforce Solution.",
  },
  {
    question: "Integrated implementation",
    answer:
      "Executing a strategic implementation is the backbone of our Salesforce consulting services. We help you with stepwise Salesforce implementation for various cloud and tools, optimize the Salesforce environment, and provide technical and strategic guidance to enhance your business and achieve maximum ROI.",
  },
  {
    question: "Building User Adoption Strategy",
    answer:
      "To help your users to master the new system, we create a user adoption strategy, which comprises iterative user training, timely user support by the Salesforce admin, release notes, and rewards for advanced Salesforce users.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce CRM Training",
    answer:
      "Our seasoned Salesforce Consultant leads your employees' in-house and onsite Salesforce CRM training sessions. The training sessions are designed to ramp up teams for better Salesforce adoption and enhanced productivity. We train your staff to become Salesforce enablers by teaching them to work smartly and innovatively.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Support",
    answer:
      "Providing support and maintenance is one of the most vital points of our Salesforce Consulting Services. We help you maintain a productive Salesforce environment with tailored support services matching your requirements. Our 24/7 reliable and effective continuous administration, monitoring, bug fixing, and resolution services ensure optimum growth for your business.",
  },
];
export const salesforce5WeOffer = [
  {
    question: "Remote Call-In",
    answer:
      "We use remote-call in a pattern when you have a remote system that performs updates in the Salesforce org. Simply put, the remote system can create, retrieve, update, or delete the data you store in the Lightning platform.",
  },
  {
    question: "Request and Reply",
    answer:
      "When you want to send the data to an external system and bring it back to Salesforce for updation, we go with the Request and Reply pattern. We ensure that the Salesforce API does the first call out in this pattern.",
  },
  {
    question: "Fire and Forget",
    answer:
      "We prefer this pattern when it is optional for a sent request to wait for a response. This particular Salesforce integration pattern has multiple solutions to resolve the issue. Due to the queue and retry mechanism, it guarantees message delivery.",
  },
  {
    question: "Batch Data Synchronization",
    answer:
      "If you have data that needs to be synchronized between two systems, we prefer to use the Batch synchronization pattern. It allows seamless data extraction and retrieval without hampering daily operations.",
  },
  {
    question: "UI Update Based on Data Changes",
    answer:
      "We prefer UI Update based on data changes when the user needs to be informed that data has arrived, ensuring he receives updates occurring in another system and has the updated data in the Salesforce system.",
  },
  {
    question: "Data Virtualization",
    answer:
      "When you have an external system performing operations that are not handled by or do not contain Salesforce data, we prefer a Data Virtualization pattern for Salesforce integration.",
  },
];
export const salesforce6WeOffer = [
  {
    question: "Salesforce Sales Cloud",
    answer:
      "We will be your reliable Salesforce Implementation Partner to get the most out of your Salesforce investment. We will help you implement Salesforce Sales Cloud to empower you to make informed decisions and improve customer acquisition, lead conversions, revenue, and productivity.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Service Cloud",
    answer:
      "If you are planning to deliver a better customer experience, we will help you achieve excellence with our Salesforce Service Cloud implementation expertise. Our Salesforce implementation experience will help you stay on top of your customer journey and make your organization genuinely customer-centric.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Marketing Cloud",
    answer:
      "Choose us as your reliable Salesforce Implementation partner and start delivering an exceptional shopping experience. We will help you empower your marketing activities and personalize campaigns to show value and stay in touch with your customers at every stage of their journey.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Community Cloud",
    answer:
      "Connect with your customers, employees, and partners and build long-lasting relationships leveraging our Salesforce Implementation services. We will customize and implement the Community cloud in your Salesforce environment to hand over control to users, offer customization as per need, and create an exceptional brand experience.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Commerce Cloud",
    answer:
      "Bacforce helps you precisely implement a trusted, flexible, and speedy commerce solution - Salesforce Commerce cloud. Enjoy digitized orders, automated orders, targeted marketing campaigns, predictive analytics, and full-fledged social media extensions for enhanced reach and increased revenue.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Financial Services Cloud",
    answer:
      "Bacforce helps banks, financial institutions, and insurance companies offer a unified customer experience with our unique Salesforce Financial Services Cloud implementation expertise. Track everything from customer information, deposits, debts, leads, referrals, and everything from a single window.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Non-Profit Cloud",
    answer:
      "Effectively manages and quantifies your programs like fundraising, grants, workforce, and more as we optimize our Salesforce implementation services to meet your nonprofit goals. Enjoy automated donor profiles, manage volunteers, enhance relationships, and achieve growth.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Health Cloud",
    answer:
      "When you have the right Salesforce Implementation Partner with you, it becomes easier for you to meet the changing demands of the healthcare industry. Quickly get a 360-degree view of patient data, experience intelligent care collaboration, and personalize the end-to-end customer experience.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Vaccine Cloud",
    answer:
      "We treat every business equally, so if you want to implement Salesforce Vaccine Cloud in your Salesforce ecosystem. We will help you integrate ethics into the vaccine management process so that you can seamlessly manage inventory, enhance patient engagement, and distribute vaccines effectively.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce CPQ",
    answer:
      "Allow us to implement Salesforce CPQ in your CRM so that you can enjoy the automated process of configuring, pricing, and quote creation. We will assist you in streamlining the quote creation per your KPIs with a vision to offer personalized and accurate quotes that lead to increased sales.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Chatter",
    answer:
      "Leverage the best enterprise social network available by leveraging our bespoke Salesforce implementation services. Organizations can use it to work securely at the workplace to share files, develop networks, declutter email, keep teams connected, and update status.",
  },
  {
    question: "Einstein Analytics",
    answer:
      "Learn the secret of turning data into insights and insights into profit by choosing us as your reliable Salesforce Implementation Partner. We will help you unravel the power of AI to streamline your customer service, sales, marketing, branding, and other business activities leading to an increase in your ROI.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce IT",
    answer:
      "Get a competitive advantage by leveraging our Salesforce Implementation Services to monetize your IoT investment. We will implement Salesforce IoT so that the large amounts of data processed by computers, sensors, and apps can be converted into meaningful insights and overcome petty business issues.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Pardot",
    answer:
      "Are you interested in implementing a B-2-B marketing automation platform in your Salesforce environment? Bacforce will be your reliable Salesforce implementation partner to ensure easy reporting ROI, get valuable sales insights, create emails to close more leads, drive more revenue, and achieve growth.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Field Service Lightning",
    answer:
      "We will enable your field service teams to do better and increase their productivity, by implementing Salesforce Field Service in your CR environment. We will customize your CRM environment so that your field services will be automated, productive, optimized, real-time, and per the company's needs. ",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Quip",
    answer:
      "We will help you implement Salesforce Quip to take advantage of the world's NO 1 CRM and collaborative productivity suite. Our Salesforce professionals will help you streamline exporting and importing live data to enhance collaboration and visibility by enabling a virtual work-from-anywhere environment.",
  },
];
export const salesforce7WeOffer = [
  {
    question: "Add, Manage and Modify Custom Objects",
    answer:
      "Get rid of standard fields and objects to revamp your Salesforce app with custom Salesforce objects and custom fields for extended functionality to improve your businessâ€™s ROI.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce Workflow Automation",
    answer:
      "Being a certified Salesforce partner, we will help you customize your existing CRM with the help of workflow rules, process builder, and apex code to simplify daily CRM tasks.",
  },
  {
    question: "Configure The Data Loader to Use the Bulk API",
    answer:
      "We can help you provide a custom Salesforce solution with operations like a collective update of records, deleting records, weekly leads evaluation, and other tasks using bulk API to streamline your business processes.",
  },
  {
    question: "Customize Reports and Dashboards",
    answer:
      "Leverage our Salesforce support services, to create customized reports and dashboards. These reports will help you identify the best/worst performing sales territories, profitable customer segments, and truthful value of your Salesforce pipeline.",
  },
  {
    question: "Custom Email Templates",
    answer:
      "Salesforce email template will help you increase your business productivity, ensuring consistent messaging. Create/modify email templates, custom style sheets, and email attachments at your convenience.",
  },
  {
    question: "Salesforce CRM Integration with Third-Party Systems",
    answer:
      "Our Salesforce developers are skilled at performing Salesforce CRM integration with third-party platforms. We use REST/SOAP API web services for effective integration and seamless data flow.",
  },
];
export const cloud3WeOffer = [
  {
    question: "Sales Cloud Consultation",
    answer:
      "The highly experienced staff at Bacforce will work in partnership with your team to understand your fundamental need or issue statement in a better way. Our skilled team of Salesforce-certified experts will find possibilities for automation in your Sales Cloud and assist you in devising a successful path to CRM implementation and usage.",
  },
  {
    question: "Sales Cloud Implementation",
    answer:
      "We have a team of Salesforce professionals experienced to handle everything related to Salesforce and Salesforce Cloud. By leveraging our Salesforce Sales Cloud services, you can increase your sales and ROI. With our expertise and skills, we will develop Salesforce Sales Cloud solutions specific to your needs.",
  },
  {
    question: "Sales Cloud Integration",
    answer:
      "Increase your sales, automate your sales process, and minimize your sale cycle by taking advantage of our Salesforce Sales cloud services. Our Salesforce experts will utilize different Salesforce features like Pardot, Lightning Dialer, Revenue intelligence, Einstein AI, Salesforce CPQ, and more to carry out effective Salesforce Cloud Integration.",
  },
  {
    question: "Sales Cloud Migration",
    answer:
      "By deploying CRM migration options that offer exact data mapping while reducing security and information problems, we assist businesses in moving from their current CRM to Salesforce Sales Cloud. We ensure optimum data security and also offer post-data migration assistance to keep you afloat.",
  },
  {
    question: "Sales Cloud Customization",
    answer:
      "Every organization faces distinctive problems that require specific answers. You may take advantage of cutting-edge Salesforce technologies that are tailored to your particular company's demands by working with Bacforce. We will develop customized Salesforce Sales Cloud Solutions to take your sales to the next level.",
  },
  {
    question: "Sales Cloud Support",
    answer:
      "Our workforce at Bacforce provides smooth and individualized support to help you overcome obstacles when implementing or overseeing Salesforce Sales Cloud. Our customer support professionals will look into your issue and provide the finest solutions.",
  },
];
